Finding Aid for Chester A. Graham Papers 1921-1980
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Alphabetical File
  - Peace
    - Dissent (Box 11)
    - Farmers (Box 11)
    - Fellowship of Reconciliation, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Government Policy (Box 11)
    - Help Avoid Nuclear Disaster (HAND) (Box 11)
    - Military (Box 11)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 11)
    - New Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam (Box 11)
    - Peace Action Coalition (Box 11)
    - Peace Caravan (Box 11)
    - Peace Education-Action (Box 11)
    - Peace Pilgrim (Box 11)
    - Political Action (Pennsylvania) (Box 11)
    - Prisoners of War (Box 11)
    - Vietnamese churches (Box 11)
    - Vietnam, various organizations (Box 11)
    - Women Strike for Peace (Box 11)
    - World Without War Council (Box 11)
  - Pentagon papers (Box 11)
  - People's Lobby (Box 11)
  - Pickens, William (Box 11)
  - Pickett, Clarence (Box 11)
  - Piney Woods School (Box 11)
  - Plans (economic) (Box 11)
  - Pocono Peoples College (Box 11)
  - Presidency (Box 11)
  - Poole, Rev. Frederick (Box 11)
  - Population Control (Box 11)
  - Pratt, George D., Jr (Box 11)
  - Priorities (Box 11)
  - Progressive Party (Box 11)
  - Public Ownership League (Box 11)
  - Public Utilities (Box 11)
  - Puncke, Fred (Box 11)
  - Purdue Rural Leadership School (Box 11)
  - Quijada, Laura (Box 11)
  - R miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 11)
  - Radio transcripts
    The transcripts of Graham's radio broadcasts in North Dakota appear to be complete. While many of the transcripts are disappointing, being more outlines of the broadcast than literal transcripts, a small but important group are word for word documents. This group is interesting because they demonstrate how Graham used the shows as vehicles to express political or social views.
    - 1948-1949, 17 folders (Box 11)
    - 1950-1953, 48 folders (Box 12)
    - 1954-July 1955, 19 folders (Box 13)
  - Religious education, 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Reuther (Box 13)
  - Riegle, Donald (Box 13)
  - Robinson, W. M. (Box 13)
  - Rohrbough, L. (Box 13)
  - Rural life (Box 13)
  - Rutledge, George (Box 13)
  - S Miscellaneous, 6 folders (Box 13)
  - Sacco-Vanzetti (Box 13)
  - Sanders, Paul T. (Box 13)
  - SANE nuclear policy (Box 13)
  - Scattergood (Box 13)
  - Schacht, Robert (Box 13)
  - Scherer, Milton (Box 13)
  - Servas (Box 13)
  - Shannondale Community House, Missouri (Box 13)
  - Sidenius, R. C. (Box 13)
  - Siddall, S. B. (Box 13)
  - Simpson, Alice (Box 14)
  - Smith, Frank (Box 14)
  - Social Action (Box 14)
  - Society of Friends
    (see also American Friends Service Committee)
    The Society of Friends material is scattered throughout the collection. Most of it is printed and only of limited interest. There are, however, minutes of a few Friends meetings.
    - Ann Arbor (Box 14)
    - Detroit (Box 14)
    - Directories (Box 14)
    - Grand Rapids
      - Meetings, 2 folders (Box 14)
      - Ministry (Box 14)
    - Green Pastures Quarterly (Box 14)
    - Lake Erie Yearly Meeting, 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Membership (Box 14)
    - Old Testament (Box 14)
  - Steer, Douglas (Box 14)
  - Stevenson, Fern (Box 14)
  - Stone, Walter (Box 14)
  - Sutherland, E. W., 2 folders (Box 14)
  - Swan, Al (Box 14)
  - T Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 14)
  - Talks and writings, 8 folders (Box 14)
  - Taylor, Wayne (Box 14)
  - Technology (Box 14)
  - Thomas, Norman (Box 14)
  - Tindall, J. S. (Box 14)
  - Tom, R. Bruce (Box 14)
  - Tone, D. K. (Box 14)
  - Townsend Plan (printed material about) (Box 15)
  - Trade (World) (Box 15)
  - Turner, Glenn (Box 15)
  - U Miscellaneous (Box 15)
  - United Nations (Box 15)
  - United States Army Ambulance Service Association (Box 15)
  - United States Constitution (Box 15)
  - Uphoff, Mary Jo (Box 15)
  - Urban League (Box 15)
  - V Miscellaneous (Box 15)
  - Vander Jagt, Guy (Box 15)
  - Venezuela (Box 15)
  - Victory Ford Committee (Box 15)
  - Volunteer Army (Box 15)
  - Voorhis School for Boys (Box 15)
  - W Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Wallace, George (Box 15)
  - Washington Trip April 1972 (Box 15)
  - Washington Watch (Box 15)
  - Weber Center, Adrian, Michigan (Box 15)
  - Wenck, Peter (Box 15)
  - "What's Cooking in Washington" by Graham (Box 15)
  - Who's Who for North Dakota (Graham entry) (Box 15)
  - Williams, Harrison (Box 15)
  - Williams, Howard (Box 15)
  - Wilson, Robert (Box 15)
  - Wisconsin (Box 15)
  - Wisconsin Summer School for Workers (Box 15)
  - Wolverine Co-operative (Box 15)
  - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom (Box 15)
  - Women's Rights (Box 15)
  - Women's Rights: "Capitol: Woman" (Box 15)
  - Workers Education Project, Wisconsin (Box 15)
  - Workers Service Projects, Wisconsin 1940 (Box 15)
  - World Federalists (Box 15)
  - "World Tomorrow" (Box 15)
  - Wyker, James D. (Box 15)
  - Y Miscellaneous (Box 15)
  - Young Men's Christian Association, 3 folders (Box 15)
  - Young Women's Christian Association, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Youth (Box 15)
  - Youth Action (Box 15)
  - Z Miscellaneous (Box 15)
  - Ziedler, Frank (Box 15)
- Photographs
  - Miscellaneous, 2 envelopes (Box 15)
    The photographs series includes portraits; views of plays, meetings, and conferences relating to Graham's work with immigrants and Americanization, and the National Farmers Union; photos of buildings and activities of Ashland College.